Serge Grigoriev/Ballets Russes Archive
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Ballets Russes: Company members; Clippings; Tour Information; Drawings (Box 10)
  - Choreographic notes for Graduation Ball, choreographed by David Lichine in 1940, Choreographed for the original Ballets Russes. (Box-folder 10/8)
Two-act version, staged and revised by Michel Fokine; Premiere: 30 November 1911, London; One-act version, staged after Lev Ivanov; Premiere: 21 April 1932, Monte Carlo
Symphonie Fantastique
Choreographer: Léonide Massine; Music: Hector Berlioz; Premiere: 24 July 1924, Covent Garden, London
Thamar
Choreographer: Michel Fokine: Music: Mily Balakirev; Premiere: 20 May 1912, Théâtre du Châtelet, Paris
Le Tricorne
Choreographer: Léonide Massine: Music: Manuel de Falla; Premiere: 22 July 1919, Alhambra Theatre, London
Union Pacific
Choreographer: Léonide Massine
Valse Triste
Choreographer: George Balanchine; Music: Jean Sibelius; Premiere: 15 August 1922
Yara
Zéphire et Flore
Choreographer: Léonide Massine; Music: Vladimir Dukelsky [Vernon Duke]; Premiere: 28 April 1925, Théâtre de Monte-Carlo, Monte Carlo